Guide to the May Chen Papers WAG.301
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: Labor, Union, Cultural, Research, Conference, and Political Materials and Reports, 1970-2017; 20.06 Linear Feet in 21 manuscript boxes, 1 flat box, 1 oversized folder, 4 oversized flat boxes, 1 half manuscript box, and 1 cassette box
  - Asian Americans and Pacific Islanders - A People Looking Forward, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Asian American Rights: New York City, 1998-2003 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Asian American Student Conference Tape #1, 1995 (Box 39, Vhs-c 301.0010)
  - Asian American Student Conference Tape #2, 1995 (Box 39, Vhs-c 301.0011)
  - Asian American Vote and US Census, 2004, 2010 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Asian American Women: Issues, Concerns, and Responsive Human and Civil Rights Advocacy, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Asian Labor Materials, 1972, 1980, 1987, 2016-2017 (Box 18, Folder 6-7)
  - Asian Labor Materials: Research on Chinese Labor, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Asian Labor in America: Challenges & Opportunities First Annual Conference, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Asian American Labor Materials, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - The Asian American Labor Movement, undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Asian Labor Class, 1996 (Box 39, Vhs-c 301.0013)
  - Asian Labor Resource Center, 1983-1984, 1988-1989 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Asian/Paciic American Heritage Festival Celebrating Pacific American Literature, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Asian and Pacific Islander American Vote (APIAVOTE), 2007 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Asian Pacific Islander Caucus Bylaws, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Asian Women, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Asian Women: Myth & Reality (Mount Holyoke College), 1981, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - "The Beat Goes On: As Study Findings are Disseminated, Impact of Joint Programs is Recognized", 2003 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Behind Closed Doors II: Another Look into Underground Sweatshop Industry, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - "Boycott's the World" Protest Song, undated (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Bulletin: Center for Transnational Labor Studies, 1999, 2001-2002 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Bumper Stickers, undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Business Agents Shop Richard Guido & Joseph Delli Carpini, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Buttons, circa 1980s-2000s (Box 41)
    Includes buttons for Jessie Jackson's 1988 presidential campaign, President Bill Clinton and Vice President Al Gore's 1996 presidential campaign, Rocky Chin's 2001 City Council campaign, pro-labor and union mottos, Mayor David Dinkins' mayoral campaign, and Michael Dukakis' 1988 presidential campaign.
  - CAAC Inflight Magazine, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Center for Working Families - Policies and Priorities for New York's Working Families, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Challenges: People and Development - "Women's Empowerment", 1995 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - A Changing Chinese America Conference, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - China, 2002-2007 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - China Aids Fund, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Chinatown & Garment District, 2013 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Chinatown Labor Fair Committee, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Chinese Consolidated Benevolent Association of New York, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Chinese CLUN Meeting (Coalition of Labor Union Women Asian-Chinese Committee), 1990-1996 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Chinese Immigration and Chinese in the United States, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Chinese News Articles, 1992, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Chinese Newspapers, 2001, 2006 (Box Shared Tamiment 081, Folder 29, Box Shared Tamiment 150, Folder 7)
  - Chinese Postcards, undated (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Chinese Press Releases, 2001-2002 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - City Originals: Women Making It Work, undated (Box 38, Vhs 301.0003-301.0004)
  - The City University of New York, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Clean Streets Chinatown: Progress Report, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Collected Articles on Garment Workers, 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Human and Trade Union Rights, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Cornell IRL - Labor Programs, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Cornell IRL School, 2010 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Cornell University "Organizing Immigrant Workers" Conference, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Cosmopolitan Orchestra Concert, 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Cosmopolitan Symphony Orchestra, 2002 (Box Shared Tamiment 150, Folder 1)
  - CPC - 41st Anniversary Celebration of Chinese New Year, undated; cuid36472 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_WAG_301_ER_3)
  - Critique of Trade Union Rights in Countries Affiliated wih the League of Arab States (Dr. George E. Gruen), 1996-2001 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - CUNY/Labor Ed., 2004-2005 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - CWE (Consortium for Worker Education), 2003 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Day Care Fashion Show, 1990 (Box 39, Vhs-c 301.0012)
  - Dear Diane: Questions and Answers for Asian American Women, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Defend the Garment Industry! Mass Rally Poster, 1998 (Box Shared Tamiment 150, Folder 3)
  - Dinkins, undated (Box 39, Vhs-c 301.0009)
  - Dinkins Election and Unity House, 1988-1990 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Doris Ling, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Drum Major Institute for Public Policy, 2006-2007 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - ECASU 2002 Workshop - Sweatshops & Labor (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - The Economic Status of American of Asian Descent: An Exploratory Investigation, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Education Reading, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Event Flyers, 2001-2002 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Facts About New York City's Chinatown, undated (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Fiscal Policy Institute, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Ford Foundation APA Women, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Freedom of Information and Privacy Acts - International Ladies Garment Workers Union, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Freedom Ride, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Friends of Women Foundation, undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Garment, 2010-2011 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Garment Industry Day Care Center of Chinatown, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Garment Industry Development Corporation - Annual Report, 2001-2002 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - The Garment Industry Development Corporation - A Case Study of a Sectoral Employment Development Approach, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Garment Worker Hours Calendar, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Garment Workers and NYC Unions, 2005, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Garment Workers Union Files, 2003, 2007-2008 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - GBA China Tour '98, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - GBA (Greater Blouse Association), 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - GIDC Sourcing Pr., 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Global Thinking/Local Voices (CUNY Bulletin of Asian American/Asian Studies), 2011 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Greater Blouse, Skirt, & Undergarment Association National Association of Blouse Manufacturers - 75th Anniversary, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Hanoi, Vietnam, 2005 (Box 39, Minidv 301.0022)
  - Health Care, 2006 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Health Care Research, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - History of the World Trade Center, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Holiday Card from NY Forum to May Chen, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - "How to Try or Defend a Civil Case When You Don't Have A Lawyer" (Hon. Margaret Cammer), 1999 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Human Services for Asian Americans in Metropolitan New York, 2000-2003 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Immigrant Workers, undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Immigrant Workers Freedom Ride, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Immigrant Workers Freedom Ride Posters, 2003 (Box Shared Tamiment 150, Folder 9)
  - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions - Trade Union Rights, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - International Labor Rights Forum, 2007-2009 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union Resolution on China re: Tianament Square, 1989-1990 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - An Invitation to Chinese and Foreign Entrepreneurs Trade Talks, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Jackson in Chinatown, 1988 (Box 39, Vhs-c 301.0016-301.0018)
  - Japan Labor Review, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - "Jobs Now-Unemployed Workers Campaign" (New York Unemployment Project), 2001 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - The Joseph S. Murphy Institute for Worker Education and Labor Studies, 2009, 2011-2012 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Korean Headband, undated (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - La Fuente, A Tri-State Worker and Community Fund, Inc., undated; cuid36483 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_WAG_301_ER_17)
  - Labor Advisory Board Meeting, 2010 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Labor Brochures, undated (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Labor Reports, 2011 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Labor Rights Training Resources, 2004-2008 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Lee Lee Tribute, 2006; cuid36485 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_WAG_301_ER_19)
  - LES for DD 11/5, undated (Box 39, Vhs-c 301.0014)
  - LES for Dinkins, undated (Box 39, Vhs-c 301.0015)
  - Liberty Jobs, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Manhattan Borough President Scott M. Celebrate Lunar New Year and Year of the Dragon Photography Susan Soo 2/22/2012, cuid36475 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_WAG_301_ER_6)
  - Many Paths, One Goal: Organising Women Workers in Asia, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - May Chen: Notebook and Address Book (Chinese Labor Tours), 2011 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - May Chen Notebook: Chinese Labor Tours, 2005-2006 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - May is Labor History Month! Poster, 2012 (Box Shared Tamiment 081, Folder 28)
  - Mayor David Dinkins & Search Committees, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 7-8)
  - Medals, undated (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Memorandum - Rights of Undocumented Workers Under NLRA, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Memorial Notebook for Professor Lee C. Lee, 2006 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Men's Day Skit, 1990 (Box 39, Vhs-c 301.0008)
  - Misc Articles (some by May Chen), undated (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - "Multiculturalism and American Trade Unions" (Cornell University, ILR School), 1991 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Mutianyu Great Wall Cable Car Corporation Ltd, undated (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - National Asian Pacific American Bar Association - Civil Rights Committee 1998 Resource Handbook (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - National Asian Pacific American Bar Association Convention, 17th, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - National Asian Pacific American Bar Association Convention, 18th, 2006 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - National Confederation of Autonomous Trade Unions, undated (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - New York City Action Summit for Latino/Immigrant Worker Safety and Health, "Making Difference", 2010 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - New York City's Chinatown Garment Industry: A Critical Case of Ethic Enterprise and Worker Organization, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - New York City Department of Enviromental Impact Report on One Police Plaza Security Plan, 2006 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - New York City Transit, 1985, 1999, 2008 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - New York Civic Participation Project, 2006-2008 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - New York Fashion Space, 2003-2004 (Box 27, Folder 3-4)
  - New York Industrial Retention Network, 2000, 2003, 2007 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - New York Industrial Retention Network Memos, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - New York State Council, 2008 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - New York Times Magazine - "The Union Kids", 1996 (Box Shared Tamiment 080, Folder 14)
  - New Youth Forum Banner, undated (Box Shared Tamiment 150)
  - Newspaper Clippings - Women's Forum, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - NG Slater Invoices & Textile Samples, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - NGO Forum '95 on Women - The Fourth World UN Conference on Women, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - NGO Forum on Women - Asia Pacific Souvenir Booklet, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - NGO Forum on Women (Beijing), 1995 (Box 27, Folder 11-12, Box 28, Folder 1)
  - NGO Forum on Women - Beijing '95, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - NGO Forum on Women - Beijing (Chinese Women Series Booklets & Brochures), 1995 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - NGO Forum on Women, Beijing - Program, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - NGO Forum on Women - Brochure, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - NGO Forum on Women - Bulletin, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - NGO Forum on Women - A Collection of Theses on "Women's Studies in China", 1995 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - NGO Forum on Women - Gala Reception Invitation, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - NGO Forum on Women - Look at the World Through Women's Eyes, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - NGO's Report on the Situation of Foreign Migrant Women in Japan and Strategies for Improvement, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - NGO Women's Conference in Beijing, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 11, Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Norman Hill APRI, undated (Box 39, Minidv 301.0020)
  - Northeastern Illinois University - Workplace Learning, 1994, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - NY92 - NY is Fashion, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - NY Membership Database, undated; cuid36488 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_WAG_301_ER_16)
  - NY Politics - Squadron, 2008; cuid36470 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_WAG_301_ER_1)
  - NYC Action Summit for Latino/Immigrant Worker Safety and Health "Making a Difference", undated; cuid36484 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_WAG_301_ER_18)
  - NYC Central Labor Council, AFL-CIO Annual Dinner Dance and Awards Ceremony, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - NYIRN - Manufacturer's Almanac, 2007 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - NYIRN - "Wake Up and Taste the City", 2003 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Office of the Mayor Proclamation - "Chinese Heritage and Culture Week", 1987 (Box Shared Tamiment 079, Folder 32)
  - Our Movement, Our World - Union Women's NE Summer School, 2014 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Outlines History of the Chinese in America, undated (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Paying the Price: Worker Unrest in Northeast China, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Photo Album, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Photo Album - Birthday and Immigration Project Staff, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Photo Album - Family, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Photo Album - Peace Demonstration, Baltimore Harbor Place Chinese Embassy, Wong Case Rally, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Photos, 2008; cuid36471 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_WAG_301_ER_2)
  - Pins, undated (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Po Ling Ng, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Po Ling Ng's School Board Election Campaign Materials, 1993, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 6-7)
  - Postcards, undated (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Poster: Activist Bill of Rights, undated (Flat-file-folder 2, Tray 2)
  - Poster - Tea & Justice Documentary (Signed), 2007 (Box Shared Tamiment 150, Folder 12)
  - Princo Budget, undated; cuid36477 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_WAG_301_ER_8)
  - A Profile of the Chinese Community in New York, undated (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Project on Independent Verification of Compliance with Code on Conduct in Garment Industry, undated (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - The Prospect of the Lower East Side Historic Landmark District, 2006 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Protecting and Growing New York City's Industrial Job Base, 2005 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Putting Gender on the Agenda: A Guide to Participating in UN World Conference, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Q&A In Cultural Diversity, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Quaker Bulletin Service- American Friends Service Committee, 1995 (Box Shared Tamiment 150, Folder 2)
  - Reading Packet May Chen Contemporary Issues in Labor Spring 2009, cuid36481 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_WAG_301_ER_14)
  - Re-Elect Po Ling Ng Poster, 1996 (Box Shared Tamiment 150, Folder 5)
  - A Reference Guide to the Overseas Chinese History, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Report to Congress of the US-China Economic and Security Review Commission, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Reports on Immigrant and Youth Labor, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Research: Garment Workers - New York City, 1997-1998 (Box 31, Folder 3-4)
  - Research Papers, 1992-1993, 1996, 2000-2001 (Box 31, Folder 5-6)
  - Restavek No More - Eliminiating Child Slavery in Haiti, undated (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Revitalizing Chinatown Business: Challenges and Opportunities (Asian American Federation), 2008 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Rising to the Challenge - Asian Student Unity Conference, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - San Francisco's 1938 National Dollar Store Strike: An Opportunity for Change (Angela Y. Lean), 1993 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - "Sixities" Student List, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Slaying the Dragon, 1988 (Box 38, Vhs 301.0005)
  - Stephen Chan Photo Exhibition, 2001-2002; cuid36479 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_WAG_301_ER_12)
  - Stiched Up By Big Brands Poster, 2000 (Box Shared Tamiment 081, Folder 30)
  - "Subsidizing Sweatshops", 2008 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Summary Report: Asian Pacific Islander Workers Hearing, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Sweatshop Slaves: Asian Americans in the Garmet Industry (Kent Wong, Julie Monroe), 2006 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Temporary State Task Force on the New York City Community School Board Elections Final Report, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Tenement Museum ESL, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - A Tenement Story (Tenement Museum), 2004 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Thesis on the Work of Guangzhou Trade Unions by Chen Weiguang, 2009 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Transitions: The Changing Profile of New York Chinatown, undated; cuid36478 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_WAG_301_ER_11)
  - Travel Joural - Trip to Japan, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Triangle Fire Commemoration Photos, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 11-12)
  - Triangle Shirtwaist Factory, 2010-2013 (Box 33, Folder 1-2)
  - Turn Around American Health Care - AFL-CIO, 2008 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Unions, 2007-2009 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - United Farm Workers AFL-CIO of American Patch, undated (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - United Hebrew Trades Division of the Jewish Labor Committee Newsletter, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Urban Agenda, 2004-2006; cuid36469 (Box 33, Folder 7, Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_WAG_301_ER_22)
  - "US Unions Resume Talks after 20 Years" (Leigh Jenkins), 2002 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Vassar, 1997-1998 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Videos for Waging Peace, undated; cuid36482 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_WAG_301_ER_15)
  - Vietnamese Women in Science & Technology, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - A Voice for Every Worker, undated (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Volunteer Organizing Committee (VOC) - UFCW, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Waiting on Equality: The Role and Impact of Gender in the New York City Restaurant Industry, 2010 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Where is Home? - A Conference on the Past & Future of Chinese Americans, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Without Ceremony: Asian Women United, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Women's Health - Fourth World Conference on Women, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Women and Health (World Health Organization Publications), 1995 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Women, Ink - Books on Women and Development Booklet, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Women Thinking Globally Acting Locally: On the Road to Beijing and the 21st Century, 1994-1995 (Box 34, Folder 6-7)
  - Women in Tottori Japan, undated (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Women of Yunnan Province, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Women's Wear Daily (WWD) Newspapers, 2003 (Box Shared Tamiment 150, Folder 11)
  - Workers Rights Reports, 2006-2009 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - The Workers United Will Never Be Defeated, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Working USA: The Journal of Labor and Society, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Wu, 2004, 2010,2014 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Yeshiva Garments W/S, 2006 (Box 39, Minidv 301.0021)
  - YKASEC, 2006-2008 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Zuni DTV, undated (Box 38, Vhs 301.0001)
- Series IV: Post-9/11 Chinatown & Lower Manhattan Development Corporation, 2001-2008; 1.31 Linear Feet in 3 manuscript boxes
  This series focuses upon Chinatown's economic recovery after September 11, 2001, as well as development efforts in Lower Manhattan designed to aid in this process. Materials include administrative documents relating to the Lower Manhattan Development Corporation and the Chinatown/Lower East Side Zone progam, newspaper clippings, brochures, and research studies. This series also contains some born-digital materials.
  - 9/11, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - 9/11 Training, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Applicants for 9/11 Apparel Bidders, undated (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Chinatown Access and Circulation Study Final Report (LMDC), 2004 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Chinatown After September 11th: An Economic Impact Study, 2002 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Chinatown Development Conference, 2007 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Chinatown/Lower East Side Empire Zone, 2002 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Chinatown/Lower East Side Empire Zone Administrative Board, 2007-2008 (Box 35, Folder 8-9)
  - Chinatown/Lower East Side Empire Zone Administrative Board Meeting, 2005-2008 (Box 36, Folder 1-4)
  - Chinatown/Lower East Side Empire Zone Hotel Committee Meeting, 2008 (Box 36, Folder 5-6)
  - Chinatown/Lower East Side Empire Zone Program, 2007 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Comments on Regs for 9/11 Bidder Registry, undated (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - CT Health Partnership, 2001-2002 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Grant Proposal - 9/11 Fund, LMDC (Lower Manhattan Development Corp), 2001-2002 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Ground One: Voices of Post 9/11 Chinatown, 2005; cuid36474 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_WAG_301_ER_5)
  - Lessons Learned from a Program to Sustain Health Coverage After September 11 in New York's Chinatown, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Listening to the City: Remember and Rebuild (LMDC), 2002 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - LMDC, 2003 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Lower Manhattan Development Corp, 2004 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Lower Manhattan Development Corp (LMDC) - "World Trade Center Memorial and Redevelopment Plan", 2005 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Moving On: Chinese Garment Workers after Septembe 11 - Working Paper for the Social Impact Working Group on New York City's Recovery from September 11, 2003 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Rebuild Chinatown Initiative: The Community Speaks, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - "Recession and 9/11: Economic Hardship and the Failure of the Safety Net for Unemployed Workers in New York City" (Annette Bernhardt and Kate Rubin), 2003 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Research Papers Post 9/11 Reports, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 6-7)
  - "September 11: Two Years Later" (WWD Newspaper Clippings), 2003 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - "Stop the LMDC Cover-Up!", undated (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - World Trade Center Memorial and Redevelopment Plan Final Generic Environmental Impact Statement, 2004; cuid36487 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_WAG_301_ER_21)